LX Jordon Bobo

(801) 386-3402 Millcreek, UT. 84124 jordon.bobo@outlook.com github.com/JordonBobo linkedin.com/in/jordon-bobo/

Summary:

2 years of experience developing and maintaining computer scripts. Strong analytic skills that made it possible to adhere to federal compliance standards in systems with protected information. Currently involved in a full stack education program with the University of Utah.

Technical Skills: JavaScript ReactJS Node.JS MySQL

MongoDB HTML/CSS Heroku Handlebars

Projects:

Middle Earth Supplier. March – April 2021. middleearthsupplier.herokuapp.com

Collaboration with 3 other programmers to build an online retail website with fictional products to demonstrate functionality and style. Has an employee section which requires a login to access.

GitHub repo: github.com/JordonBobo/MiddleEarthSupplier

Tools used: Handlebars, MySQL, Sequalize, Express, Node, GSAP, Bootstrap, jQuery

Travel Quiz. January 2021. jordonbobo.github.io/JSQuiz02-Travel/

A small fun quiz app that lets users answer questions to get travel suggestions. Built for mobile or desktop users.

GitHub repo: github.com/JordonBobo/JSQuiz02-Travel

Tools used: JavaScript, jQuery, CSS, HTML, Bootstrap

Alpha Investments. January 2021. jordonbobo.github.io/AlphaInvestments/

An investing website that shows company information, stock performance, and current news headlines for publicly traded US companies. Collaboration project with 4 other programmers.

GitHub repo: github.com/JordonBobo/AlphaInvestments

Tools used: Chart.js, Ajax, Alpha Vantage API, NYTimes API

Experience:

Utah Higher Education Assistance Authority (UHEAA). Salt Lake City, UT.

Systems Support Specialist (May 2019 – February 2021)

- Extensive multitasking in order to complete overlapping projects and tasks without overlooking any key system or variable.
- Fostered a collaboration focused environment to develop, maintain, and improve inhouse software.

Processor (January 2018 – May 2019)

• Exceeded all expected accomplishment standards by more than 20% with the lowest number of quality assurance issues in the department.

Murray City Corporation. Murray, UT

Library Services Aide (November 2013 – July 2017)

- Facilitated the library's acquisition and implementation of new ILS software and Self Service Machines.
- Administered meetings which concluded how to best utilize \$50,000+ annual capital expenditures budget.

Education:

University of Utah Coding Bootcamp (November 2020 - May 2021)

Intensive training program to gain exposure to full stack programming.

Utah State University. (Graduated May 2013)

Bachelor of Arts in History.